National Service Secretariat Records
National Service Secretariat (US) Records
- Resource material, miscellaneous (arranged by format)
  - Miscellaneous video recordings, Titles are given as written on the tape.
    - Coalition for National Service (9-14-88 Master), 09/14/1988; nat_serv_sec_019; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic (Box 49)
    - Coalition for National Service 3/4" Dub (Version #2: w/out credits), 11/20/1988; nat_serv_sec_020; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic (Box 49)
    - Coalition for National Service (version #3: w/credits), 11/20/1988; nat_serv_sec_029; VHS (Box 49)
    - Coalition for National Service 3/4" Dub (Version #3: w/credits), 11/20/1988; nat_serv_sec_021; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic (Box 49)
    - Don, Graphic over name (2), nat_serv_sec_024; All Graphics for Video: (1) Title, (2) Don’s title superimposed, (3) Linda’s title, (4) Credits, (5) Don’s address.; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic SP (Box 49)
    - Dub Tape for National Service Final Edit tape (T-2), nat_serv_sec_025; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic SP (Box 49)
    - Final Edit Master for National Service Video, 9/85; nat_serv_sec_022; label on the cassette case reads: "Robin M. Noonan, Graduate Thesis Project"; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic SP (Box 49)
    - Moving Around: National Service in Trinidad and Tobago, May 1991; nat_serv_sec_031; VHS (Box 49)
    - The National Service Alternative (1988 version), nat_serv_sec_018; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; running time 10:00 (Box 49)
    - The National Service Alternative V-1, nat_serv_sec_028; VHS; running time 14:00 (Box 49)
    - National Service Re-Dub (6), nat_serv_sec_026; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic SP (Box 49)
    - National Service Video Dub #1 Final, nat_serv_sec_023; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic SP (Box 49)
    - T-9: The National Service Alternative, nat_serv_sec_027; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic SP; running time 14:00 (Box 49)